var italian = [
	{
		front: "the boy",
		back: "il ragazzo"
	}, {
		front: "the girl",
		back: "la ragazza"
	}, {
		front: "the man",
		back: "l'uomo"
	},{
		front: "the woman",
		back: "la donna"
	}, {
		front: "the family",
		back: "la famiglia"
	}, {
		front: "the house",
		back: "la casa"
	}, {
		front: "the food",
		back: "il cibo"
	}, {
		front: "hello",
		back: "ciao"
	}, {
		front: "good morning",
		back: "buongiorno"
	}, {
		front: "good evening",
		back: "buonasera"
	}, {
		front: "goodbye",
		back: "addio"
	}, {
		front: "please",
		back: "per favore"
	}, {
		front: "thank you",
		back: "grazie"
	}
];

module.exports = italian;